

Hasnat Saimun

- O Cumilla, Bangladesh
- **8801755048017**
- @ hasnatsaimon020@gmail.com
- http://hasnat.virtualitprofessional

Skills	
Laravel	
РНР	
Bootstrap	
css	
javascript	
Wordpress	
wordpress	
Github	
Languages	
Bangla	
English	
Hindi	

Hi, I am a full-stack web developer with 2+ years of experience in PHP programming. Being a php related CMS I can help you with any kind of WordPress and Laravel issues like error fixing, bug fixing, creating new projects or migrating from one CMS to another.

Profiles

nasnat-saimun

Certifications

Web Development with PHP & Laravel

2024

Ostad

https://ostad.app

Experience

Virtual IT Professional

2024-Present

Backend Devoloper

Cumilla, Bangladesh

https://virtualitprofessional.com/

On Virtual IT Professional I'm playing the junior backend developer rule since February 2024. We work to build any kinds of Management system software, CRM and any kinds of website development related task.

Education

Cumilla Govt. College & University

2020-Present

Accounting

Accounting

https://www.cgcc.edu.bd/

Certifications

Web Development with PHP & Laravel

2024

Ostad

https://ostad.app

Experience

Virtual IT Professional

2024-Present

Backend Devoloper

Cumilla, Bangladesh

https://virtualitprofessional.com/

On Virtual IT Professional I'm playing the junior backend developer rule since February 2024. We work to build any kinds of Management system software, CRM and any kinds of website development related task.

References

Md Abu Yousuf

Founder & CEO of Virtual IT Professional

https://www.abuyousuf.info